Eduardo Elías Chacón Web Developer

Portfolio Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Linkedin eduardo.elias.1192@gmail.com
GitHub

Professional Profile

Professional with experience in web development and customer service. Noted for advanced technical skills in web programming, using relevant technologies. Focused on customer satisfaction and process optimization. Capable of combining software development knowledge with solid experience in technical support to provide effective solutions. Committed to continuous learning and new challenges in the IT sector.

Work Experience

Web Developer Front-End - Igrowker

June 2024 - Present

 Development of a mobile-first web app aimed at efficiently managing events. This project is designed to generate positive impact and growth in developers' skills and competencies, ensuring technical and commercial viability.

Web Developer Front-End - Makisan Tech

June 2023 - December 2023

 Development and maintenance of applications and web pages, to improve the user experience and optimize project performance.

Customer Service - Manpower Inc

March 2017 - February 2019

 Resolution of technical problems, sales and promotions, technical support, account management, complaint handling, case tracking, achievement of objectives.

Customer Service - Movilnet

September 2013 - November 2016

 Resolution of customer queries and complaints, technical support in telecommunications services, customer satisfaction guarantee.

Academic Training

Full Stack Developer Core - Digital Nao x Tecmilenio

October 2023 - May 2024

Interdisciplinary web development:

- Front End (user-facing interfaces and systems)
- Back End (logic, servers, and databases)

Developer Full-Stack - Egg Cooperation

December 2022 - September 2023

 Introduction to programming, Java, MySQL databases and React.js. It also included aspects such as object-oriented programming, exception handling and database connections.

Web Developer Front-End - Eidos Global-Accenture

March 2023 - June 2023

 Program designed to strengthen skills in Front End technologies, such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap and GitHub, with the aim of enhancing web development and collaboration on projects.



Technical Skills

JavaScript Java **React JS Astro Node JS HTML & CSS Spring MVC Bootstrap** Tailwind-CSS **MySQL** Github **Postman** Wordpress Jira **Trello Notion** Miro **Figma**

Vercel

Technical Skills

Optimal Systems Management
Optimization of Processes
Computer Consulting
Computer Assistance
Customer Service
Quality Control
Technical Support

Soft Skills

Logical and Analytical Thinking
Effective Communication
Attention to Details
Time management
Teamwork
Adaptability
Creativity

Languages

Spanish - Native English - A2